{
  "topic_id":"10",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "which one of the statments is correct.",
      "choice": [
        "my grandmother grew up in witemere.",
        "st.marry",
        "i would like to become a famous writer like sydney sheldon",
        "Dear Bryan, Yours faithfully"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "The ansewer is 4th one. ",
      "keywords": [{ "correct": "ትክክል" }]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "which one is correctly punctuated",
      "choice": [
        "No it isn’t seven yet.",
        "“After a while,” he added, I was walking without a cane",
        "My mother-in-law’s photograph album",
        "he she and me'"
      ],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "will shows future action , the second option is correct but for past action so the answer is 'studies'",
      "keywords": [{ "My mother-in-law’s": "አማት" }]
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which sentence is capitalized correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "The planet nearest the sun is mercury.",
        "the Planet nearest the Sun is Mercury.",
        "The Planet nearest the Sun is Mercury.",
        "The planet nearest the Sun is Mercury."
      ],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [{ "nearest": "ቅርብ" }]
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which sentence is capitalized correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "I walked Home with Cindy.",
        "I walked home with Cindy.",
        "i walked home with Cindy.",
        "I walked home with cindy."
      ],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which sentence is capitalized correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "'That,' We were informed, 'Is a snow leopard.'",
        "'That,' we were informed, 'is a snow leopard.'",
        "'That,' We were informed, 'is a snow leopard.'",
        "'That,' we were informed, 'Is a snow leopard.'"
      ],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        { "informed": "አሳወቀ" },
        { "snow": "በረዶ" },
        { "leopard": "ነብር" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which sentence is capitalized correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "On a cloudless night, I studied pisces, a constellation in the northern sky.",
        "on a Cloudless Night, i studied Pisces, a constellation in the Northern Sky.",
        "On a cloudless night, I studies Pisces, a constellation in the Northern Sky.",
        "on a cloudless night, I studied pisces, a constellation in the northern sky."
      ],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [
        { "cloudless": "ደመና የሌለው" },
        { "constellation": "ህብረ ከዋክብት" },
        { "sky": "ሰማይ" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which sentence is capitalized correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "I have shopped for clothes from the gap on the store's website.",
        "i have shopped for clothes from the Gap on the store's Website.",
        "I have shopped for clothes from the Gap on the store's website.",
        "i have shopped for clothes from the gap on the store's website."
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [{ "shopped": "ተገዝቷል" }, { "clothes": "አልባሳት" }]
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Choose the sentence with correct capitalization and punctuation.",
      "choice": [
        "Are we going to dinner at 5 30 P.M.?",
        "Are we going to dinner at 5:30 P.M.",
        "Are we going to dinner at 5:30 P.M.?",
        "Are we going to dinner at 5:30 PM?"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [{ "dinner": "እራት" }]
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which of the following sentence is capitalized correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "A tale of two cities",
        "A Tale Of Two Cities",
        "a Tale of Two Cities",
        "A Tale of Two Cities"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [{ "tale": "ተረት" }, { "cities": "ከተሞች" }]
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which of the following sentence is capitalized correctly?",
      "choice": [
        "'can we go home?'",
        "'can we go Home?'",
        "'Can we go Home?'",
        "'Can we go home?'"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": [{ "home": "ቤት" }]
    }
  ]
}
